假象!
Of illusion!
何谓现实,,何谓魔术?
What is real and what is magic?
正是你们想知道的
This is what you will wonder
我的表演让你们震惊!
as I perform feats that will astound you!
正如所见,,袖子里没有东西
As you see, there's nothing up my sleeves.
帽子也只是普通帽子
And this hat is just an ordinary old hat.
看我挥三下
Watch as I wave three times above the hat
轻语魔咒
and whisper the magic words.
现在
And now.
这不行, 已经破了
It's not working. It's ripped.
没事儿, 宝贝,,只是个小洞
It's okay, baby.It's just a little tear.
赶快, 妈妈
Hurry up, mom.
你们担心什么?
What are youso worried about?
Sally会嘲笑我们
Sally's gonna makefun of us.
Sally ayersman?
Sally Ayersman?
她说她的裙子是精品店买的
She said her mom boughther dress,at bloomingdale's,
而我们是你自己缝的
and you had to make ours.
我们会出糗
We're gonna look stupid.
还记得我们昨晚听的?
We were listeningto yesterday?
那个唱诵[尊重]的女士?
That lady who sangabout respect?
Reetha?
Aretha, 正是
Aretha.That's right.
底特律长大会很有钱吗?
Do you think she had lots ofmoney,growing up in detroit?
什么是底特律?
What's detroit?
一个城市, 我想说的是
It's a city. The point is
她依旧是最棒的歌手之一
that she's one ofthe best singers ever.
倘若Sally再嘲笑你们
If sally's mean to you again,
我会锁住她爸爸的敞篷车
I'm just gonna have to key,her daddy's new convertible.
你们知道那意味什么?
Do you knowwhat that means?
[小美人儿]
little bittypretty one
[过来和我说说话]
come on and talk to me
[小宝贝儿]
lovely dovey dovey one
[过来坐在我腿上]
come on sit downon my knee
与Chase, House谈过了吗?
Speak to chase and house yet?
纪律审查听证会
The disciplinary hearing.
McGinley案件
The mcginley case.
不是2个星期
That's not for two weeks.
明天
Tomorrow.
日程安排失误
Scheduling disaster.
你不会想知道
You don't want to hear it.
你要让他们准备就绪
You've gotta get the boys' okay,to move the hearing up
要提供法律咨询
and you've gotta do that,whole legal advice thing.
能让别人做吗?
Can you ask someone else?
我想让你做
I'm asking you.
让我和Chase共事
Let me work with chase.
House已将律师开除
House should have separate counsel.
不管你期望什么,,别指望了
Stop looking for ,whatever you're looking for.
整个月
For the last month,
House都在吹嘘,你不能继续与他工作
house has been crowing,that you can't work with him
因为你已浑然爱上他
because you're just swooning in love.
我此刻无法感到
There is nothing
对他的一丝爱意
approaching love in,what I feel about him right now.
如果你不能与他共事
Well, if you can't work with him,
结论依然
it amounts to the same thing.
我们吵过一架
We had a fight.
很尴尬
It's awkward.
为何不找其他律师?
Why not use another lawyer?
因为去年40%的投诉案,都关于House
Because 40% of our lawsuits,last year were about house.
不能与他工作
If you can't work with him,
不能在这里工作
you can't work here.
她表现过激
She's overreacting.
你溜进她办公室
you snuck into her shrink's office
偷览她的私密文件
and read her private file.
尼克松那样做时
When nixon did that,
被当场抓获
he got impeached.
所以你的意思是
So you're saying
我不能和一个实习医生口交?
I'm not allowed to have oral sex,with an intern either?
是的!
Yes! And yes.
那文件让我有幸发现
That file got me,on the floor of her attic
她围墙下的内心世界
with her pouring out her soul.
唯一我做错的是：被逮到
The only thing I did,wrong was get caught.
Chase在哪儿?
Where's chase?
下班前他都没空招待你
He's too busy to service you,until after work.
我倒是有些时间
I've got a couple of minutes though.
欢迎交谈, 比如
Feel free to say something like,
[下班前, 我们能做点什么]
"what'll we do with the time leftover?"
你可以先酝酿
Or you could just stew.
同样奏效
That works as well.
她发怒前会先酝酿
She stews before she gets violent.
这份是你,明天会出席听证会
This one says you're okay with moving,the disciplinary hearing to tomorrow.
这份是我,已向你解释法律权利
This one says I've advised,you of your legal rights.
我需要知道,什么法律权利?
Uh-huh. Any legal rights,I should know about?
没有
Nope.
很好
Great.
而你以为这就是[尴尬]
And you thought this was gonna be awkward.
你不该签字
You shouldn't sign it.
[延缓]总是上全之策
Postponing's almost always,the smart thing to do.
稳定情绪
Tempers cool.
记忆模糊
Memories fade.
他们会做出裁决
They rule on me,
就这样, 对吧?
it's done, right?
是的, 但
Yeah, but--
让我们一口气把它弄完
then let's get it over with.
你做过[同级评审]吗？
Have you ever done,a peer review before?
没有
No
很好
Good.
[同级]是错误用词
"Peer" is a misnomer.
他们是你上级
These are your bosses.
这会赔上钱财
This'll could cost you some money,
职权
some privileges,
亦可能赔上你的事业
or it could cost you your career.
我只能说出经过
All I can tell them is what happened.
[经过]都有可观面
There's an objective,reality to what happened.
委员会不会知道
And that committee's,never gonna know it.
他们只知道被描述的[经过]
All they're gonna know is,what they picture happened,
一部份取决于你[说什么]
which depends a little,on what you tell them,
和一大部分你[怎样说]
and a whole lot on how you tell them.
5月11日
May 11th.
病人来门诊复查
The patient presented to the clinic--
她的名字?
what's her name?
文件里有
It's in the file.
你知道吗?
Do you know it?
运用
Then use it.
Kayla, 就诊症状为复合关节
Kayla, presented to ,the clinic with multiple joint
以及胃部疼痛
and stomach pain.
Foreman医生执行神经诊测
Dr. Foreman was called in,for a neurological consult.
这样做的目的是什么?
What's the point of this, man?
检查你妹妹的脑协调性
Checking your sister's ,cerebral coordination.
是腿和胃的状况
The thing is in her leg and her stomach.
6小时就是教她玩游戏?
Wait in the clinic for six hours,so she can play patty cake?
昨晚你本该出现在急诊室
You could've gone to the er last night.
是吗?,那你来照顾孩子们?
Oh, yeah? You gonna come,over and baby-sit her kids?
病人家属难缠,我明白了
okay. Patient comes,from a family of jerks.I get it.
能药物控制吗?
Can you stick to the medicine?
什么异常?
Something wrong?
有葡萄膜炎
there's some uveitis.
含义?
meaning?
她眼膜红肿
Her iris, the colored part of her eye,
整个眼球发炎
was inflamed.
含义?
Meaning?
最坏情况, 会瞎
Worst-case, blindness.
但亦有乐观一面
But there was an upside.
足以激发House兴趣
It was weird enough ,to get house interested.
年轻女人, 关节疼痛
Young woman, joint pain.
淋病是种可能性
Gonorrhea's a possibility.
关节骨
It's probably articular.
或许类风湿?
Maybe rheumatoid?
那指小关节,而她疼到膝盖
That's typically small joints. ,This hit her knee.
高安动脉炎
Takayasu's arteritis.
拿个血清样本
Get a sed rate and serologies.
儿童禁触
Childproof.
似乎无数孩子,被[伟哥]侵害
Like how many kids, are hopped up on vicodin?
给我
Gimme.
好啊
Right.
好像我真得不行,Chase
Like I'd ever get it back. Chase.
忽略[伟哥]
don't care about the vicodin.
不仅在动脉病发
Might not just be her arteries.
可能蔓延到所有血管
It could be all her blood vessels.
脉管炎
vasculitis.
伴有胃痛,所以是白塞病
With stomach pains.So behcet'S.
不, 该有口疳
No, she'd have oral sores.
阴道炎
Or genital.
去查明
Go find them.
我以为她是Foreman的病人
I thought she was foreman's patient.
为什么你做检查?
Why did you do the exam?
该有口疳
she'd have oral sores.
或阴道炎
or genital.
去查明
Go find them.
哇, 哇, Foreman
Whoa, whoa, foreman.
Chase能处理骨盆
Chase can handle the pelvic.
哪里疼吗?
Any pain?
很糟糕吗?
Is it bad?
会很快结束
This would go a lot easier
如果你和我交流
if you'd talk to me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只是很讨厌医院
I, um, I just really hate hospitals.
我12岁时
When I was 12,
扁桃体发炎
I had my tonsils out.
必须停课,不能吃冰激凌
Got to skip school,lots of ice cream.
因此我想成为医生
Made me want to be a doctor.
我8岁时母亲去世,所以...
My mom died when I was eight so...
普林斯顿医院陪伴数月
I spent months at princeton general.
你妈妈因酗酒而妄?
She'd died of dt's,your mom?
酒瓶藏在每个角落?
Bottles stashed around the house?
心神不宁?,难以应付?
Mood swings?That whole deal?
你经历过?
You've been there?
是我妈妈,因父亲的抛弃
My mom. Dad left.
妈妈一头钻进酒瓶子
Mom crawled inside a bottle.
使我高3那年丰富多彩
Made for a great,year 12 of high school.
你现在和父亲相处甚好?
You okay with your dad now?
不好
No.
这故事你父亲知道吗?
Does your dad have anything, to do with this story?
不, 只不过
No, it's just--
好吧, 我明白了,你们两个同病相怜
okay. I get it.The two of you bonded.
为什么你未被投诉
Which is probably whyyou haven't been sued.
病人不会控告,爱戴的医生
Patients never suedoctors they like.
但抓住重点, 好吗?
But keep it brief, okay?
听审团不想,感到被人操控
The panel doesn't like to think ,they're being manipulated
正当被操控的时候
when they're beingmanipulated.
她有溃疡反应
She had some ulceration.
确诊为白塞病?
Confirming behcet's?
我开给她波尼松,一种解酸药
I gave her someprednisone, an antacid,
并在胳膊上做了病理检测
and I ran a pathology teston her arm.
化验结果要等24小时
Takes 24 hoursto confirm.
并告诉她任何医生,都可以解读
I told her any doctorcould check it out.
你没有安排复诊
You didn't makean appointment.
没有, 她自己出现
Nope. She just showed up.
是吗
Uh-huh.
Chase医生
Dr. Chase.
好的, 我来看看
Hi. All right.Let's take a look.
小脓疱说明为阳性
Okay. Those little pustulesmean ,it's positive.
去找护士Preven
Talk to nurse preven.
和Brustin医生预定,风湿诊疗时间
Get an appointment with,dr. Brustin in rheumatology.
白塞症容易治愈
Behcet's is very treatable.
你很快会康复
You're gonna be fine.
好的, 谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
你正在聊电话
you were just chatting ,on the phone with someone
她过去打断你
and she happenedto run into you.
事实如此
That's what happened.
无预约?,无检查?
No appointment?No real examination?
只给她化验结果
Just gave herthe test results.
所以是敷衍了事
So, lower standard of care.
你没注意到,任何潜在症状
You really couldn't be expected to notice,there was anything else wrong.
我们甚至没进体检室
We didn't even gointo an exam room.
作为你的律师,我不能阻止你说谎
As your lawyer, I can'tstop you from lying.
我不能参加听审会
I can't even bein the room.
不能教你把谎说得圆满,则是我失职
But I would be remiss,if I didn't prep you to lie better.
你写给她一张处方
You wrote hera prescription,
说明有过一个检测
which means there wasan examination.
究竟发生过什么?
What really happened?
我正在讲电话
I was on the phone.
Chase医生?
Dr. Chase? Hi.
嗨
Hi.
Kayla, 我来复诊,胳膊?
Kayla. I'm herefor the test. My arm?
噢, 是的
Oh, uh, yeah.
唔, 好的
Um, okay.
成阳性,去找Rreven护士
It's positive.Talk to nurse preven.
和Brustin医生,预定风湿诊疗时间
Get an appointment with,dr. Brustin in rheumatology.
我服用你开的药
I took that medicineyou gave me,
但胃痛依旧
but my stomachstill hurts.
白塞症比想象的严重
The behcet's can bestronger ,than we thought,
亦可能是波尼松的反应
or if could be refluxfrom the prednisone.
是种更强的抗酸药
Here's a stronger antacid.
医生?
Doctor?
是的?
Yes?
算了
Nothing.
你没问她胃痛?
you didn't ask her anything ,about the stomach pain?
我犯了一个小失误
I made onelittle mistake.
小失误演变成大失误
As little mistakes go,that was a biggie.
她只协助Chase,而你呢?
She's only advising Chase?,Not you?
委员会能把我怎么样?
Well, what's the committee,gonna do to me?
我甚至没见过这位病人
I never even metthis patient.
你与生俱来的轻蔑态度,不能为你开脱
Your disdainfor human interaction,doesn't exculpate you.
将你牵连
It inculpates you.
你在文件上签字
You signed the charts.
Chase做的每件事,你有连带责任
You're responsible for,everything chase does.
这是不必担心的原因
Which is why thisdoesn't matter.
她袒护Chase,等于袒护我
She protects chase,she protects me.
除非她对Chase的建议是
Unless her adviceto chase,
以放弃你为交换条件
is to make a dealand give you up.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
假设House医生,可以多加留心
If only dr. Househad paid attention.
他甚至未见她一面
He never even met her.
他从未这样做过
He never does.
Chase爱我,不会背叛我
Chase loves me.And isn't turkish.
Cameron爱你,Chase爱他的工作
Cameron loves you.Chase loves his job.
你确实认为Stacy如此恨我?
You really think,stacy hates me that much?
我认为此刻,她对你的恨超出极限
I think right now ,she hatesyou more than enough.
你以为情绪只会,影响医生的判断?
You think emotion only,affects doctors' judgments?
事情会因你们的,亲密关系而蔓延
Everything stemmed ,from that one interaction.
他们会推究于你
They're gonnaslam you on it.
开小差?,是你的错
Were you distracted?Your problem.
超时工作?,是他们的错
Overworked?That's their problem.
健忘? 你的错,懒...
Forgetful? Yours.Lazy--
我以为胃痛是白塞症状
I just figured the stomachpain ,was the behcet'S.
任何医生都会如此判断
Any doctor would'vethought the same.
为何又打给她,在她离开后一小时?
Then why did you call her,an hour after sheleft the clinic?
Preven护士说,你让她把Kayla召回来
Nurse preven saidyou asked her,to have kaylacome back in.
是因为她欲言又止
The way she hesitated.
我以为她有难以启齿的问题
I thought she might've had,a doorknob question.
病人问诊
Patient comes in.
说他一直流鼻涕
Says he's gota sniffly nose.
你为他做10分钟的检查,对吧?
You examine him,for ten minutes, right?
于是你准备离开
Then you're leaving,,hand on the doorknob,
此时他却说
and he says, "oh, yeah,
[我的睾丸一直勃起]
and my penishas turned green."
尴尬的也是,关键性问题
Embarrassing question,only important one.
病人最后才会启齿,你知道
Patient saves it for last.So you knew
她就要提出,最关键性问题
she was about to ask,the most important question
而你离开了
and you left.
不, 我并没有
No, I didn'T.
事后我才意识到
I figured it out later.
什么被改变?
What changed?
什么也没改变
Nothing.
糟糕回答
Bad answer.
在第一时间,我没考虑周全
I wasn't thinkingclearly at first.
更糟回答
Worse answer.
如何能修复这个问题?
So what washer doorknob question?
我想到她可能便血
I figured it might be,blood in her stool.
迹象是溃疡出血
Which could indicatea bleeding ulcer.
和我说
Talk to me.
35岁女性大量呕血不止
35-year-old femalevomiting,massive amountsof blood.
工作时病倒,血压80到20
Loc at work,bp 80 over 20.
心率120
Heart rate 140.
血能止住吗?
Push fluids?
局部流失3升,正试图静脉注射
Three liters in the field,,and we're bolusinganother one right now.
会是溃疡物大出血
It's gotta bea bleeding ulcer, doc.
工友说她像吃糖,一样服食镇痛药
Co-workers said she's been,eating ibuprofens like candy.
我以为她是白塞症
I thoughtshe had behcet'S.
到达胃部
I'm in the stomach.
太多血了我看不到
There's too much blood I can't see.
大动脉爆裂?
She burst an artery?
不, 那里, 泳出来
No. There. Bubbling.
只是个大溃疡物
Just a bad ulcer.
我正在缝合
I'm cauterizing.
-看不见, 增加盐水,-等等
- Can't see.Use some more saline.- Hold on.
好的
Okay.
看起来不错
Whew. Looks good.
溃疡出血,控制住了
Bleeding ulcer.We got it.
两个小时前她还很好
She was finetwo hours ago.
心室收缩,血压70
Systolic bp 70.
溃烂在哪儿?
Where's the ulcer?
是褐色的,我刚缝合
It's brown.I cauterized it.
一定是别的,那里...
There must besomething else. There.
二处溃疡?
second ulcer?
不, 是穿孔
Not anymore.It perforated.
把她送去急救室!
Get her to an O.R.!
外科医生缝合穿孔
The surgeons were, ableto suture the perforation.
但病人的溃疡细胞
But the contentsof the patients--
kayla胃里的溃疡菌,扩散到体内
kayla's stomach had ,spilledinto her body.
她转为败血症
She got septic.
感染使血压下降
Then the infectionlowers ,her blood pressure.
每点50帕斯
50 over palpat one point.
侵害肝和肾
It damagedher liver and kidneys.
我明白这很糟糕
Listen, I knowthis looks bad.
明显是我诊断错误
I obviously gotthe diagnosis wrong.
但我是照常理操作
But I did everythingby the book.
我不能预知将发生的状况
I couldn't have known,what was going to happen.
不喝咖啡,我会发脾气
If I skip my coffee,I get cranky.
你想要点什么?
Do you want anything?
Chase为什么搞砸?
why did chase screw up?
他忘记一个提问
He forgotto ask a question.
需要理由吗?
Does there needto be a reason?
可能救他
It might help him.
至少我认为是一个小失误
As far as I'm concernedhe, made a little mistake.
时而发生
It happens.
你考虑得多远?
How far areyou concerned?
你认为我存有偏见?
You think I'm biased?
你们是同事
You're colleagues.
你们同事超过一年
You've worked together,for over a year.
大家说你们睡过
And everyone says,you slept together.
谁说的?
Ahem. Who says?
正确答案是,[我们无牵连]
The correct answer is,,"we're not involved,
[我无偏见]
and I'm not biased."
我们无牵连
We're not involved.
我不知道他为何失误
And I don't know why,he messed up.
House和他共事更久
House has worked with him,longer than I have.
你应该和House谈
You should talkto house.
是啊
Yeah.
Chase为什么会搞砸??
Why did chase screw up?
因为他对病人不闻不问
Because he doesn't give,a crap about patients.
他总是得到病人正面反馈
He always gets positive  patient reviews.
用尽84颗牙齿微笑
Yeah. Smiles all84 of his teeth.
讲述他那扁桃体故事
Tells themhis tonsil story.
动听的故事
It's a nice story.
他还留着他的扁桃体
He still has his tonsils.
从他走出办公室一刻起
As soon as he's out of the room,
或者将要走出办公室一刻起
which is as soon as,he can be out of the room,
他已准备开讲,那垃圾故事
he starts inon the trash talking.
自以为和House一样
Thinks not giving a crap,makes him like house.
像是一个值得,效仿的榜样
Like it's somethingto aspire to.
我必须作证吗?
Am I gonna have totestify?
我不鼓励他们传讯你
I won't be encouraging them, to call you.
House怎么说?
What'd house say?
持续两个月
Two months like this.
让我猜猜,没卖保险
Let me guess.No insurance.
刚听说免费诊疗
Just heard aboutthe free clinic.
不错的起点
It's a good move.
你不想因此,影响必要开支
You don't want to ,skimpon the essentials
比如腕表和MP3播放器
like wristwatchesand mp3 players.
我要和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
在门口?
From the doorway?
是机密
It's confidential.
很好, 我喜欢说闲话
Cool. I love gossip.
听到那劈啪响?
Hear that crackling sound?
好像揉纸球?
Like crumpling up paper?
继续听
Keep listening.
变声告诉我
Let me knowif it changes.
两个问题
Two questions.
为什么Chase搞砸?,有多严重?
Why did chase screw up?,And how bad was it?
说起效率
Wow.Talk about efficient.
我只有一个答案
I only need one answer.
Chase没有搞砸
Chase didn't screw up.
他说他有
He said he did.
我不是律师
Well, I'm not a lawyer,
但好像是个,失败的法律策略
but that seems like,a sucky legal strategy.
他们想知道
They're gonna want to know
作为一个医生,你认为Chase为何会那样
what you think a reason able doctor ,would'vedone in chase's position.
如果我认为他,是个正常的医生
If I thought he wasa reasonable doctor,
我不会聘他
I wouldn't havehired him.
天啊,你们真是珠联璧合的一对
God, you two area couple of geniuses.
将一切否决
Denying everything.
彻底耍弄律师
Completely fool the lawyer
谁会帮你
who's trying to help you.
太糟糕,陪审团恰巧都是医生
Too bad the reviewcommittee members,are actually doctors.
Stacy.
Stacy
到达胃里
I'm in the stomach.
太多血,看不到
There's too much blood.I can't see.
静脉爆裂?
She burst an artery?
不, 那里
No. There.
涌出的地方,只是个恶性溃疡
Bubbling.Just a bad ulcer.
好的, 我在缝接,不错
Okay. I'm cauterizing.Looks good.
溃疡失血,已被控制
Bleeding ulcer.We got it.
两个小时前她还很好
She was finetwo hours ago.
如果你的[很好]
If by "fine,"
指血像喷泉一样,从穿孔飞出
you meanshe had fountains of blood,spurting outof every orifice,then,
那样, 我相信你
yeah,I believe you.
估计那些是欢庆响铃声
I'm guessing thoseare celebratory bells.
心室抽缩,血压70
Systolic bp 70.
溃疡处在哪
Show me the ulcer.
是褐色的,我缝接过
It's brown.I cauterized it.
让我看到整个胃部
Sweep back. ,Show methe whole stomach.
停
Stop.
二处溃疡?
second ulcer?
把她送去急诊室!
Get her to an O.R.!
我们走
Let's go.
2小时前她不是[很好]
She was not finetwo hours ago.
她提到胃痛?
She mentionstomach pain?
-是的, 我给她更强,-你没检查?
- Yeah, so I gave hera stronger--,- you didn't do an exam.
她是突然出现
She just came infor a follow up.
拿病理结果
The results ofthe pathogy test.
你检查胃部了吗?,要害部位?
Did you listen to her stomach?,Check her vitals?
或许她提过止痛药
Maybe if she hadsaid something,about takingibuprofen.
提到直肠出血
Mentionedthe rectal bleeding.
是啊,为什么她不像你一样去读医学院?
Yeah, why didn't ,she goto med school like you did?
痢疾,便血
Diarrhea,blood in the stool.
-这些常规问题,-医生们总是跳过
- These areroutine questions--,- that doctorsskip all the time.
那是个小失误
It was a minor mistake.
我不能预料
- I couldn't have known--,- mistakes are as serious
误诊和直接致死一样严重
as the results they cause.
这女人会因,你的懒惰而死亡
This woman could die ,because you were too lazy
-一个简单的问题,-不, 她可能身亡
- to askone simple question.- No, she might die
因为我倒霉得,撒了你的[伟哥]
becauseI had the bad luck,to spillyour damn vicodin pills.
而我要回答一连串尖锐审问
And I responded with ,a numberof trenchant remarks
可能会把Chase吓哭,所以这些不是我的证词
which made chase cry,,none of which I'm gonnatestify about.
除非你让Chase归罪于我
Unless you convincechase ,to roll on me.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
证实什么?
Testify about what?
唔...咕咕声
Uh...chuck.
我来打破[缺德医生]寓言
I'm gonna breakfrom the parable,of the wicked doctor
讲一个病人的故事
and tell a little story about a patient.
姑且叫他...[币]
Let's call him...buck.
血氧饱和度低下,噼啪的肺音
Who has low o2 satsand, crackling lung sounds.
就像我
Like I have.
[币]患有特发性纤维病
Buck has idiopathicpulmonary fibrosis.
他肺片正在硬化
His lung tissue'sturning to rock.
无前例,无药可医
There's no known cause,,no treatment.
他会窒息而亡
He is slowly suffocating.
你说的是我?
You're talking about me?
肺移植费用是50万美金
Lung transplants about,half a million dollars.
但这个笨蛋没买医疗保险
But this poor sucker'sgot no insurance.
如果打算现在补办
And if he triedto sign up now,
会以[已知]为由被拒
he'd be excluded.Pre-existing condition.
让我先和律师求证
But let me confirmwith my lawyer.
得到证实
She confirms.
除非[币]购买保险前
If only buck hadn't been,diagnosed with fibrosis
未被诊断出纤维变性
before he got insurance.
继续刚才话题
So, back to the exam.
你这样通知他死讯?
That's how you tellthis guy he's dying?
放松, 他只是感冒
Oh, relax.He's got a cold.
马上, 会买保险
And soon,health insurance.
多么英雄,纠正错误
Such a hero.Always righting wrongs.
谁在乎被你纠正?
Who cares who youhave to manipulate?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我竟不知道,原来你和[币]关系这么好
I never realized youand buck were so close.
道德的一个方面
It's a point of principle.
并不能改变我偷窥的事实
Right. It's gotnothing to do ,with what I didto you.
对你我无话可谈
There's nothingfor us to talk about.
这就是你跟踪我的原因
That's whyyou're following me.
我不过阅读几篇笔记
I read some notes.
-如果Chase就此自毁前程,-我错了
- If chase screwed up--,- I was wrong.
我发自内心抱歉
I'm terribly,terribly sorry.
如果Chase的失误如此严重
If chase screwed upso badly,
为什么不解雇他?
why didn'tyou fire him?
因为他头发漂亮
He has great hair.
你隐瞒什么?
What are you hiding?
我是同性恋
I'm gay.
那不是你的意思
Oh, that's notwhat you meant.
但解释很多疑点
It does it explaina lot though.
没有女友,总和Wilson一起
No girlfriend.I'm always with wilson.
整天惦记着球鞋
Obsession with sneakers.
腹泻, 便血
Diarrhea.Blood in the stool.
6个月前你早该,问得两个简单问题
Two simple questionsyou could've ,asked her sixth months ago
从而避免目前这一切
andaverted this whole thing.
你一个都没问,为什么?
You didn't ask either.Why?
由你的问题和态度判断
Judging from your question,and your demeanor,
我想你刚和House谈过
I assume you werevisiting with house.
已说过,我不知道
We've been over this.I don't know.
-好医生从不犯错?,-好医生从不会忘记
- Good doctors don'tmake mistakes--,- good doctors never forget
提出问题?
to ask questions?
你已得到答案
Then you've gotyour answer.
我显然不是个好医生
ApparentlyI'm not a good doctor.
[自哀]不是辩论之策略
Fyi. Self-pity generallyis not ,a good strategy in these hearings.
手术后发生的事情?
What happenedafter the operation?
肾脏损伤并不严重
The kidney damageisn't so bad.
肝脏损伤令人忧虑
The liver damage ismore worrisome.
肝脏不可被透析
There's no dialysisfor livers.
我知道,但如果切除一片肝
I know, but if sheloses a liver,
可以移植一片, 对吧?
she can geta transplant, right?
可以把她列入名单
We can put her on a list.
我能捐献
I could do it.
我给她我的肝
I could give her partof my liver.
外科医生不会执刀
Surgeons won't operateunless the donor's
除非捐献者深思熟虑
had a long timeto weigh the decision.
可以去黑市
There's black markets.
-买器官, 那只是,-噢, 我的胃!
- For organs,that's just--,- ow! Ow, my stomach!
-疼痛持续?,-是啊!
- The pain constant?,- Oh, yeah!
-刺痛或钝痛?,-我不知道
- Sharp or dull?,- Oh, I don't know.
-已硬化,-噢!
- It's firm.- Oh!
有些凉
It's a little cold.
-有腹水,-不, 是血凝块
- She's got ascites.-No, it's a clot.
护士! 准备急救室
Nurse! Call the O.R.
准备做栓子切除手术
We've gotta prep her,for an embolectomy.
CBC, 理疗和专家组
And a cbc, pt,and a liver panel.
败血症使血压持续下降
The sepsis had loweredher bp so much
肝内有血块
she got clotsin her liver.
挡住肝脏动脉,切掉输血管
They blockedthe hepatic artery,,cut off the blood flow.
肝脏压力过大
Her liver was shocked.
Cubby依然将她列入名单?
And cuddy listed her?
在如此多发症状下?
With all the other problems?
不行
Forget it.
不能把肝脏给,这样的晚期病人
We can't give a liver,to a woman this sick.
你知道你在说什么吗?
Do you listen to whatyou're saying?
没理由为血管炎病人,装个新肝
There is no pointin giving a new liver,to somebody who also has vasculitis.
可医治
Treatable.
加上肾脏败坏
And kidney damage.
改善中
It's healing.
你知道她致死的真正原因?
You know what'sreally killing her?
Chase忘问一个,胃痛的基本问题
Chase forgot to ask a standardquestion ,about stomach pains,
所以他误诊
so he missed the diagnosis,
所以她穿孔,所以她有败血症
so she perforated,so she got sepsis,
所以她血压爆升
so her bp tanked,
所以她有血凝块
so she got blood clots,
所以她肝脏被割
so she lost her liver.
肝脏之重要
Livers are important, cuddy.
无之丧命
Can't live without 'em.
所以才叫肝脏
Hence the name.
这才是问题关键
And here's the big issue.
Chase是医院的职员
Chase isa hospital employee.
而kayla
And kayla
是养有两个傻孩子,的可怜母亲
is a sympathetic motherof those ,two jury-friendlymoppets caleb and cody.
Dory和nikki
Dory and nikki.
综上所述,,你是归咎于Chase
Your point, beyond justtrying to make,chase wet himself,
看来医院正面临医疗事故
seems to be that ,the hospital facesliability here.
谢谢, 做出总结
Well, thanks for clearing that up.
我仍需要一个医学理由,帮她申请
I still need a medicalreason to list her.
这就是医学理由
That isthe medical reason.
病人家属打赢医疗事故官司
The family wins thishospital in a lawsuit,
他们将要搬进临时公寓
they'll turn itinto condos.
临时公寓外有列长队,等待被医治的病人
And people will die waiting outside, a condofor medical care.
祷告着什么时候,才能轮到自己
Start praying for, a 12-car pile upon the turnpike,
因为我们正在浪费肝
because we're not exactly,swimming in livers over here.
你列席作证时
When you're testifying,
跳过House打败,Cuddy这一部分
skip the details on ,howhouse convinced cuddy.
我不认为
I don't think
得不到捐献的病人,需要知道原因
the people who got bumped down the ,transplantlist need to know why.
不再重要
It didn't matter anyway.
她下一个得到捐献?
she next on the list?
-是的,-但她抗体呈阴性
Yes.But she's ab negative.
非常少见
Very rare.
她还能撑多久?
How long can she go on like this?
大概一两天?
Probably anotherday or two.
我捐献我的肝
I'm donating my liver.
-Sam我们正谈这个问题,-我是最佳体质
- Sam, we've talkedabout this.- I'm a perfect match.
六分六蛋白质抗原
Six out of sixhla proteins.
这么快得到化验结果?
How'd you getchecked out so fast?
化验室有我熟人
I know a guyin medical testing,
花钱买插队
and I paid himto rush it.
Sam贿赂某人,提前自己化验?
Sam bribed someone to rush his tests?
你不会吗?
Wouldn't you?
某人会因此而被归咎
Someone's gonna get,the blame for what happened.
事情越铺越广...
So the more we spread itaround,
你说没有外科医生愿意
might as well--,you said no surgeon would do
在此情况下动手术
a live donor transplant ,on such short notice.
House也把它办妥
House took careof that too.
你的病人血凝块严重
Your patient'shardly clotting.
维他命Q取代K,和上次手术产生的血凝块
Sub q vitamin k ,and freshfrozen plasma pre-op.
孤注一掷
Pretty risky.
正是我来拜托医院,最棒移植手术医生的原因
Well, that's why I cam to the ,best transplantsurgeon in the hospital.
只有你能救她
She's dead without you.
下午把她送过来
Get her in this afternoon.
非常感谢
Whew. Thank youvery much.
应该的
My pleasure.
我猜这是你胡编,的暖身用语?
And this was right before ,you ran the marathon, I suppose?
你指[握紧双手,以示谢意]那部分?
Was it the part wherehe warmly ,clasped my hands in thanks?
有些过头哦?
Was that too much?
你对他作过什么?
What did you do to him?
医院律师问我,是否有不道德行为
The hospital lawyer asks me,if I did something unethical.
如果有,也是最后一个告诉律师
If I did, the last person ,I'dtell is the hospital lawyer.
值得强调,她对我已失尽信心
Especially since she's gone,all old testament on me.
你会告诉我
You'll tell me.
那好吧
Oh. Okay then.
一个告诫
One caveat.
我已厌倦[三方性交]
I've movedpast threesomes.
对[四方性交]又无兴趣
I'm not into foursomes.
一人背信退出
Someone backs out,
至少你还有[三方性交]
then you've still gota threesome.
如果两人退出
And if two peopleback out,
至少还是性行为
you're still having sex.
-哪怕三个人, 你仍会震惊,-你说都是辨方证词
- You'd be amazed.Even if three people--,- anything you sayis attorney-client.
你终于明白[大事不妙],自我折磨
So you get advice aboutthe bad, bad thing, you did knowing that I'll be tortured
无法清楚阐述观点
because I can't tell a soul.
实际上, 那经历不错
Actually, it is kindof cool.
你彻底疯了吗?
Are you completelyout of your mind?
她怎样都会死
She's dying on her own.
我为何志愿做刽子手?
Why would I volunteer,to be her executioner?
我怎样都会被病人家属
I'd just be invitinga lawsuit ,from the brother no matter what.
5000美金,只是首付
Five grand. And that'sjust ante money.
手术完成,还有1万5
After the surgery,you get another 15.
但提醒你,小费在内
Though I warn youthat includes the tip.
我一年挣60万
I make 600 grand a year.
我会为区区2万,自毁名声?
You think I'm gonna risk,tanking my percentages for 20,000?
免税
It's tax-free.
说到档案...
For the record...
我希望委员会,把你和Chase
I hope the department ,takes you and chase
一起从医院后门踢出去
and drop kicksboth your asses,out the back door.
很好
Great.
意味我不用担心
That means I don'thave ,to bother welshing on the 15 grand
还欠你1万5
I would've owed you.
如果你不做手术,我就告诉你老婆
If you don't do the surgery,,I'm gonna tell your wife
你和多少护士睡过
that you've been sleepingwith ,a series of nurses.
目前是辐射科Culter护士
Currently nurse cutlerin radiology.
60万除以二是多少?
Now what's 600 granddivided by two?
上年圣诞晚会
Last christmas party.
Cutler护士递给你一个小热狗
Nurse cutler handed youone ,of those little hot dogs,
你并没说谢谢
and you didn't thank her.
那只发生在,你非常非常亲密的人身上
Well, that only happens ,whenyou're very, very intimate.
以及
That and the fact
你一直敞着裤门儿,跳来跳去
that you've been practically dancing ,around withyour zipper open
鞋底粘着一条,用过的保险套
and a used condomstuck on your shoe.
显然你老婆,是唯一不知情的人
Your wife is apparentlythe only one ,who doesn't know.
你敢告诉她
There's no wayyou'll tell her.
我当然不敢
Of course I won'T.
我是胆小鬼
I'm much too cowardly.
我会寄匿名信
No, I'll just sendan anonymous letter.
今天下午四点,我预定一间手术室
Now I've got an O.R. Booked,for 4:00 this afternoon.
你有空吗?
Are you free?
提到个人档案
Oh, and for the record,
你是医院里,最差的移植手术医生
you are the worst transplant surgeon ,in this hospital.
但不巧
But unfortunately,
你是目前,唯一背叛妻子的
you're the only one who's currently ,cheatingon his wife.
你贿赂,接着恐吓他?
You bribed him and then,you blackmailed him?
她只剩两天
She'd have been deadin two days
我只能逼Ayersman做手术
if I hadn't made ayersman,do the surgery.
听证会上,务必跳过[恐吓]这段
Leave the blackmailout of the story,you tell the committee.
和你谈话前,本打算跳过
I tried to leave it,out of the story I told you.
停车场的插曲呢
And then there was that incident, in the parking lot.
不要这样,你疯了!
Don't do that.Wait! Are you nuts?!
我没!,我没背叛你!
I didn't do it!I didn't do anything!
给我钥匙!
Give me the key!
显然某人寄给他妻子,一封匿名信
Apparently someone sent, an anonymous letterto his wife.
你恐吓Ayersman,在他执行手术后
You blackmailed ayersman,,he performed the surgery,
你仍然出卖他?
and you ratted him outanyway?
似乎不公平, 是吧?
Doesn't seem fair, does it?
你无法控制自己！
You just can't controlyourself, can you?
不过多么愚蠢
No matter how stupid,
-多么自毁,-使本次谈话顺利进行
- how self-destructive--,- to make this conversation easier,
我们置其它于一边
can we discard the fiction,that we're talkingabout anything
先说我对你做过的事?
other than what I didto you?
我溜进你那,精神病专家的办公室
You're not mad because ,I broke intoyour psychiatrist's office.
是啊, 我是兴奋,好吧, 确实下贱
- Yeah, I was thrilledabout that.- Okay, it was a lousything to do.
如果被发现的是少女日记
But if what I'd found,that was everything was all kittens
或者月光宝盒
andmoonbeams in markville,
你不会如此介意
you'd be over it.
不, 我会的
No, I wouldn'T.
你生气是因为,我全盘告诉你
You're mad at me ,forletting you know what I did
因为你希望顺其自然
because you likedwhere things were going.
因此, 我很对不起
And for that,I actually am sorry.
非常愚蠢
It was stupid.
讲个关于病人的故事
Let me tell you ,a storyabout a patient.
一个病人, 姑且叫她[釜山]
A patient we'll call fusan.
因为Sam提前拿到化验结果
because sam had rushed his tests,
我们当天下午,将他们推进手术室
we were able to get them ,into surgery that afternoon.
Ayersman医生成功完成,肝移植手术
Dr. Ayersman performed ,the live donor transplant.
他切除左肺叶,移接血管
He resected the left lobe, ampatic vein,
动脉管接上Sam的肝
ampatic artery of sam's liver,
将其移植到Kayla身上
and transplanted it into kayla.
手术很成功
The operation was a success.
Kayla和Sam,接受常规护理
Kayla and sam continued ,to receive routine care.
2个月后...
Two months later...
她来复诊
she came by for an exam.
7月24日,保持严谨
July 24th.Be precise.
你做的体检?
You did the exam?
-坦白说, 我只...-坦白? 刚才为止都在说谎?
- Honestly, I just--,- honestly? So you've beenlying up till now.
我们作个交易
Let's make a deal.
我不用[坦白]
I won't usethe word "honestly",
你必须停止
and you'll quitstopping by
[House不满情绪],发泄在我身上
to see house so you don't take it ,outon me afterwards.
如何?
How about that?
我希望尽量远离Kayla
I wanted to be as far away,from kayla as possible.
House逼我上阵
But house was rubbingmy nose in it.
孩子们好吗?
How are the girls?
她们很好
They're great.
Dory的初恋
Dory hadher first crush,
漂亮的男孩
which was cute.
是吗?
Oh, yeah?
但她初次分手
And then her firstsort of breakup,
完成得并不漂亮
which was not so cute.
温度很高99.3
You're hot. 99.3.
-有咳嗽吗?,-没有
- Have you been coughing?,-No.
-小便疼痛吗?,-没有
- Pain in urinating?,-No.
99度并不很高, 对吗?
99's not that high,is it?
免疫抑制剂引起发烧
Immunosuppressantsblock fevers.
不该发生在你身上
You shouldn't haveone at all.
我让护士提取你的培养物
I'm sending a nurse, in hereto draw cultures.
需要作一个X光
And I'm orderinga chest x-ray.
我没再出错
I wasn't makinganymore mistakes.
又一个避免的词汇
Another phrase to avoidin, front of the committee.
一小时后,她再度高烧
She spiked her feveran hour later.
AST和ALT均高出标准
Her ast and alt are up.
她对新肝排斥
She's rejecting the liver.
不, 只是感染
No. It's just an infection.
一个培养物已移出球菌团
One of her cultures isgrowing out strep.
只有一个?,可能是污染物
Just one?Probably a contaminant.
出现脱水,血球容量过高
She's dehydrated.Her hematocrit's up way.
污染物
It's strep.
转氨酶也在增多
Transaminasesare up too.
-只是污染物的应激反应,-Chase, 你和这个污染物
- That's just stressfrom the strep.- Jeez, chase.You and this strep.
已开过房
Get a room already.
她并没出现排斥
She's not rejectingthe liver.
只是感染,她会没事儿的
It's just an infection.She'll be fine.
最坏打算,可以二次移植
worst case, we could relist her.
你是House?
You house?
呃, 看情况
Well, that depends.
你准备殴打,House医生?
Are you gonna hitdr. House?
你从未面诊我妹妹
You haven't evenseen my sister,
你和我耍花样?
and you're beingcute with me?
Sam我们正在谈论她
Sam, we're talkingabout her right now.
-她的发烧可能是...-可能是甲型, 乙型肝炎, 对吗?
- Her fever might be--,- could be hep b, hep c,right?
可医治, 你给她干扰素
It's treatable.You give her interferon.
她没事儿, 对吧?
She's okay. Right?
你对肝炎了解不少
You know a lotabout hepatitis.
他刚把肝捐出去
He just donated his liver.
你脸红了,你病了?
You're flushed.You sick?
我很累
I'm tired.
你在掩饰生病的事实
You're hiding the factthat you're sick.
为什么这样做?
Now why would you do that?
嘿, 你干什么
- Hey, what are you--,- either you specifically asked for
要么是特意晒伤纹身
a tattoo of a heart that's been ,leftout in the sun too long,
不然就是自己纹的
or that is a reallybad home job.
常见引发肝炎的途径
It's a very common wayof getting hep c,
恰巧你有
which you have.
你患病已久
You've had it a long time.
否则我不能捐献
It was gonna keep me,from giving my liver.
你贿赂实验室人员,证明你没病?
You paid off that lab tech to say, you were clean?
几年内无病发
It hasn't beenactive in years.
-她会死,-你贿赂某人?
- She was gonna die--,- you paid someone off?
真缺德
That istotally unethical.
立刻为他和妹妹做MRI
Get and mri for himand, his sister right now.
她被我感染肝炎, 对吗?
She got hep from me,didn't she?
没有, 没有, 当然没有
No. No, no, no.God no.
我想她因你得上肝癌
I think she gotcancer from you.
House是正确的?
House was right?
Sam有颗恶性肿瘤
The brother hadan ,undiagnosed hepatoma
附随在被移植的肝脏上
that was transplantedwith his liver.
Kayla体内迅速滋长
It grewa lot fast in kayla
因为她免疫系统低下
because she wasimmunosuppressed.
House怎么知道?
How could househave known?
肝炎可能引发肝癌
Hepatitis can causeliver cancer.
加上她的血细胞比容
Plus, her hematocrit,
红血球比例过高
red blood cell count was high.
通常引发脱水
Usually means dehydration.
极少情况转为癌症
Rare cases, cancer.
可能救了Sam一命
It probably savedsam's life.
早为他做切除手术
We were able to operate, on him early enough
在恶化之前
before it metastasized.
Kayla已出现,肝排斥反应
Kayla had already started,rejecting the liver.
因为癌症而不能,二次获得捐助
And you couldn't re-list her,because of the cancer.
我们无能为力
Nothing we could do.
很好
This is good.
哥哥隐瞒自己肝炎
The brother lying about his hep.
是介入行为
It's an intervening act.
不是你的失误,导致癌症
The proximate causeof her cancer ,and not your mistake.
她6个月前已经身亡
She would've diedsix months ago
如果他没捐出自己的肝
if he hadn'tgiven up his liver.
或许, 无法证实
Maybe. Can't prove it.
你得跟我来
You need to comewith me.
宣读文件时间
Just been servedwith papers.
实际上只有一页
Actually, paper.One page.
被告:普林斯顿 普兰斯堡医院和
Defendantsprinceton-plainsboro hospital
Robert Chase医生,略...
and dr. Robert chase. Blah blah blah.
医疗过失, 失误,略...
Medical malpractice,negligence. Blah blah--
难以理解他们起诉Chase?
you're surprised they're suing?
爱戴Chase的人们,竟然忘记...
You think peoplelove chase so much,they're justgonna forgo--
赔偿罚金:一千万美金
punitive damages, inthe amount of $10 million.
赔偿罚金?,他们视其为医疗事故?
Punitives? That means ,they'realleging gross negligence.
他们的律师一定疯了
Their lawyer's obviouslyout of his mind.
Larry Ruseckas,他不是个傻子
Larry ruseckas.He's not crazy.
噢, 我知道,我被他告过
Oh, I know.I've been sued by him.
你一整天都在,掩饰事实胡说八道
You have been hiding ,thingsand lying to me all day.
无一句夸大其词
I haven't liedabout anything.
排除被我承认的部分
Except for the partsI admitted ,I was lying about.
而我不是被告
And I'm not the one being sued.
我感觉很滑稽
I feel funny.
你没告诉我们什么?
Well, what haven'tyou told us?
就在她出院前
Before she checked out,
Sam找到替换肝
sam found hera second liver.
-她有癌, 怎么会...-黑市
- She had cancer.How could she--,- black market.
墨西哥城有个医生,愿意做手术
There was a doctorin mexico city,who was going to dothe surgery.
她下午5点飞机
She's leavingfrom jfk at 5:00.
在小货车后备箱,会见墨西哥骗子
To meet some mexican guy ,in the back of a van
猪肝和一把电锯?,无理取闹
with a pig's liverand a hacksaw?, This is nuts!
向House打小报告?
Want to rat meout to house?
他会说有亿万分之一的可能,就去做吧!
He'll say if there's a chance,in a billion, then go for it.
这不是她期望的
This is notwhat she wants.
她在被利用,一个受良心谴责的哥哥
She is being manipulated ,by a morally guilty brother
还有一个触犯法律的医生
and a legallyguiltier doctor.
你以为她想死吗?
You thinkshe wants to die?
她怎样都会死
She's dying either way.
Chase...
你认识多少人带着黑市器官,在街上溜达
how many people you knowwalking ,around with a black market organ
来路不明的外科医生?
froma third world surgeon, huh?
这不会使你超度
This isn't gonna be your salvation.
是罪加一等
It's just one more thing ,they'll pin on you.
进去,做正确的事
Go in there.Be the good guy.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
不, 没有时间了
No, there's no time.
两分钟, Kayla...
Two minutes. Kayla...
是我的失误
I made a mistake.
我对你突发症状,不够细心
I wasn't as blunt,as I should've been about your odds.
我甚至不想面对
I probably didn't wantto face them myself.
Chase医生,请不要这样
Dr. Chase,please don't do this.
旅途压力和手术
The stress of the travel,the operation.
癌症本身
Even then the cancer.
Kayla, 我们走
Kayla, we are going.
我爸爸死于肺癌
My dad died.Lung cancer.
事发前几个月我刚见过他
I saw him a couple of months ,before it happened.
我们未提及
We never talked about it.
对你父亲的死我很难过
I'm sorry your fatherdied,
-但那根本...-他从未告诉我他生病
- but it has nothing--,- he never even told mehe was sick.
我希望被告知
I wish he had.
那会...
It would--
你就要死了
you're gonna die.
一个人,离开你孩子几千里以外
Alone. Thousands of miles,from your children.
你不想那样对她们
You don't want to dothat to them.
Kayla.
Kayla
对不起, Sam
I'm sorry, sam.
Kayla, 你不能放弃
Kayla, you can't give up.
如果你...
If you do this...
如果你回家...
if you go home...
那是我杀了你
I killed you.
不是的
No.
你给我三个月
You gave me three months.
你给Dory和Nikki三个月,与我共渡的时光
You gave dory and nikki ,three more months with me.
他们发现我的癌
And when they foundmy cancer,
也发现你的
they found yours.
而我救了我哥哥
And I got to savemy baby brother.
一个星期后,Kayla在家里去世
a week later, kayla died at home.
Sam因此发怒
Sam was furious.
所以才会有整单诉讼案
That's gotta be whythe big lawsuit.
你信吗?
Are you buying this?
当然不信
of course not.
没有非法移植,没有因果关系
There was no illegal transplant.There's no causation.
他就差杀了我
He was ready to kill me.
或者他对他的律师说谎
Maybe he's lyingto his lawyers.
或者你对我们说谎
Or you're lying to us.
上个星期四他找你做复查
Last thursday he saw you,for post-op care.
如果你恨你的医生,你可以换个医生
If you hate your doctor,,you find another doctor
但你要先换个律师
before you find a lawyer.
这个人没起诉,Cameron或Foreman
This guy didn't suecameron or foreman.
他甚至没起诉House
He didn't even sue house.
有个人因素
There's something personal here.
在听证会前,某些不想告诉我们的事实
Something you don't want us,to know before your hearing.
那次会面前,他没恨过你
The guy didn't hate ,youbefore that meeting.
他在之后才恨你
He hated you after.
生活如何?,孩子?
So how's everything else?The girls?
孩子们难过, 不停得哭
You know, a lot of crying.Some nightmares.
我们会好起来
We'll be okay though.
那就好
Good.
但孩子们不想搬家
But the girls arenot gonna be happy,about leaving town though.
她们爱那栋房子
They love that house.
后院和她们的朋友
The yardand their friends.
你们要搬家?
You're moving?
手术过后, 我就像个残废
Ever since the operation,I've been on disability.
还有债务抵押, 所以
And the mortgage, so...
搬到乡下去,找个便宜的地方
moving out of state,,somewhere cheaper.
不管怎么说,谢谢你
Anyways, thanks.
我杀了你妹妹
I killed your sister.
我误诊她的溃疡
I misdiagnosed her ulcer.
我杀了她
I killed her.
闭嘴
Shut up, man.
-她爱戴你, 就像...-我宿醉
- She liked you.Just--,- I was hungover
她找我复诊的时候
when she came back to see me.
我忍着前晚的酒劲
I'd been up halfthe night drinking,
还有头痛
had a headache,
只想尽快离开那里
and I just wanted,to get the hellout of there.
我豪不在意,你妹妹要说-
I couldn't have cared less what ,your sister was saying
她的胃痛
about her stomach pain.
我能和我的[未来前],雇员说几句吗?
May I speak to my futureformer employee?
不错的故事
Great story.
你认为我在说谎?
you think I'm lying?
确实是我和他的对话
It's exactlywhat I told him.
我确信无疑,但你向他说谎
I'm sure it is.But you lied to him.
你希望他被他起诉
You want him to sue you.
我杀了他妹妹
I killed his sister.
今早我点的是黑咖啡
I ordered black coffeethis morning
却得到奶昔,每个人都乱来
and got cream.Everybody screws up.
没人在你咖啡下毒
They didn't put poisonin your coffee.
我见过你喝醉
I've seen you hungover.
而误诊那天你并没有
You weren't the day ,you blewhis sister's diagnosis.
那有什么关系?
What does it matter why?
如果我理由充足,她能少死吗?
Is she less deadif I have a good excuse?
如果我认为,你因宿醉而失误
If I thought you screwed up,because you were drunk,
我一早就抄了你
I would've fired you.
你知道?
You knew?
你当时失落难过
You were depressedand distracted.
我猜测你接到继母的电话
And I assumed you hadgotten ,a phone call from your step-mom.
我是Robert
This is robert.
他怎么死的?
what did he die of?
不可能
That's impossible.
我两个月前才见过他
I saw him two months ago.
如果他有肺癌,他会...
If he had lung cancerhe would've--
Chase医生?
dr. Chase?
好消息是：,现在你已双亲双亡
The good news is both,your parents are dead now,
所以不存在,犯类似错误的理由
so no reason to screw upthis bad again.
你怎么知道?
How'd you know?
医院有内线
There's this interconnected ,network of computers,
被称作[局域网],你可以...
or interweb,where you can--
你怎么想到去调查?
how did you knowto look?
他来找我,说他只剩2个月
When he visited,he told me, he only hadtwo months left.
当你失误时,我做过数学
And when you screwed up,,I did the math.
为什么你不告诉我,他要死了?
Why didn't you tell mehe was dying?
他不让我说
He asked me not to.
所以你就把我凉在,无知的一面
So you just hung meout,there to be blindsided.
是的Chase,都是我的错
Yeah, chase.It was all my fault.
你可以做个选择
Look, you've got a choice.
要么说出事实
You can eithertell the truth.
医院给家属慰问金
Hospital settles.Family gets some money.
他们可以保住房子
They get to keeptheir house.
要么你继续撒谎
Or you can keep upthis lie.
家属得到赔偿金
The family gets punitive damages.
买个旅行车,搬到临时停泊区
They buy a jet. ,They move to park avenue.
你得再找一份职业
And you have to findanother career.
你什么也不会说?
You're not gonnasay anything?
我会闭嘴
I'm gonna keepmy mouth shut.
法律上,你被谴责我受益
Legally it's better for me,if you go down in flames.
Chase会和委员会,提他父亲吗?
Is chase tellingthe committee about his dad?
不知道
I don't know.
我以为你会让他出卖我
I thought you were gonna,get him to sell me out.
我不会那样做
I wouldn't do that.
为什么不?
Why not?
你亦是我的当事人
You're my client too.
是呀
Yeah.
除非你辞职,这个事实不会改变
And that's not gonna change,unless you leave this job.
或许我会
Or I do.
怎样与自己在意的,同事共事?
So, how do you dealwith a coworker,that you have feelings for,
积极或消极?
positive or negative?
我不想像Chase那样结束
I don't wantto end up like chase.
我不想被抓到,因私人感情和杀...你
I don't want to get emotionally ,caught up and kill...you.
不全是消极的
It's not all negative.
或许你是对的,或许...
Maybe you were right.Maybe--
或许那就是问题
maybe that is the problem.
那我们做什么?
So what do we do?
不知道
I don't know.
House医生?
dr. House?
经过慎重考虑,证词及相关文件
After consideringthe testimonial ,and documentaryevidence,
现在宣布对,Kayla McGinley案件的裁判
this ad hoc committee in the matter ,of kayla mcginley has reached a decision.
Chase医生...
Dr. Chase...
你的错误诊断,导致病人身亡
your error resulted in a patient's death.
并对上司以家属说谎
You also liedboth to your superiors,and the patient's brother.
但考虑到你父亲,去世的事实
But taking into account the ,mitigating factor of your father's death,
我们决定不撤销,你的医生执照
we've decided not to revokeyour privileges.
你将受到一星期,停职处罚
You'll receive one week's suspension
及终身入档
and a letter in your permanent file.
现在,对House医生
Now, as for dr. House.
没有证据表明
There is no evidenceof ,a failure to supervise
任何学术上的,领导管理失误
that would lead to disciplinary action.
但是
And yet,
足够的投诉,直指你的个人品行
there isenough in the record to be ,very troubledby your conduct,
包括恐吓信事件
including certain allegations of blackmail
针对移植手术工作组,的某位同事
from members of the transplant team
及拒绝会见病人
and by your general refusal ,to meet with your patients.
应当注意
It should be noted
你的病人仅凭,一次身体检查
that your patient's cancer,was diagnosed as a result
-就被断诊为癌症,-别提病人
- of a directphysical examination.- Not of the patient.
我见过她哥哥,没见过病人
I met the brother. Never met her.
想我每接一个病人,出席一次家庭聚会?
You want me to goto a family reunion,every timeI take on a patient?
委员会决定
The committeehas determined
至少一个月
that for no lessthan one month
House将被另一位医生,监督实习
dr. House will have his practice ,supervisedby another doctor,
被指派的是Cuddy医生
to be designated by dr. Cuddy.
本次诉讼程序休会
This proceeding is adjourned.
你知道会这样吗?
Did you know this was coming?
他们一个小时前通知我
They contacted meabout an hour ago.
那Chase呢?
What's happeningto chase?
现在你被解雇了
Now you're fired.
不, 他没有
No, he's not.
House医生,和你新老板打招呼
Dr. House,meet your new boss.